I really just wanted to say that being a representative of a place and Jeffrey Epstein having an island there does not make it acceptable for him to be telling you how to carry yourself in a congressional hearing.
For Stacey Plaskett to be an actual delegate representing the Virgin Islands, she doesn't have a vote in Congress, but she's representing the Virgin Islands, which is where Jeffrey Epstein's island was.
So for her to be there answering on his behalf, like, like being a part of the conversation, being a part of the duplicitousness means that she was in the pocket.
Now, here's the thing. People are going to say, well, maybe she had no choice.
Maybe she had to.
And what I just want, what I just really trying to understand is like, according to y'all, nobody has a choice to do anything.
That's really what that what I gather from from folks.
Nobody has a choice because they might lose their job or they might get hurt or they might lose their name or whatever.
Like nobody has nobody seems to have a choice, according to people.
Now, this is reported by The Washington Post, which is owned by Jeff Bezos.
What I'm trying to tell y'all is that they're literally using these Epstein files to play with you, to play with you.
The Democrats put out some emails the other day.
Now they got Washington Post putting out some emails against the Democrats.
Like all of this is just to distract you.
That's it.
Because everybody's bought.
They're all bought and paid for.
And many of them are really on the side of, well, this is, you know, it's Israel.
This is what it is.
You've seen your best friend Jasmine Crockett say that.
The United States is always going to have a relationship with Israel.
There's nothing that can be done about it.
Well, when y'all saying shit like that, how else will it change?
Because you're bought.
Jeffrey Epstein is more than just a pedo.
Jeffrey Epstein is a paid pedo by the Israeli folks.
And for the purpose of creating a black male relationship that can exploit and extort folks in U.S. government.
Ghislaine Maxwell's Pops is another one in the mix.
Like y'all don't, this is deep.
This is deep.
So I just wanted to bring that to y'all's attention because I feel like a lot of people really don't know the depth and so they're just reading stuff on the surface and we have to continue to acknowledge the real depth.
And the depth is that Republicans and Democrats are built on top of, they're built on top of a foundation of Zionism.
Literally, like someone said here, on Monday, the United Nations is voting to legalize the genocide and occupation of Gaza.
You know, the same genocide and occupation of the International Court said is illegal.
This is the first time that so many people can see what it is.
So let's see what we do with that.
Have a good night.